James Tuesday Paschall

Full Stack Developer

(206)499-7442 | beautuesday@gmail.com | Seattle, WA

jbfive.github.io

linkedin.com/in/jamestuesdaypaschall I github.com/JBfive codecademy.com/profiles/JBfive I codewars.com/users/JBfive

Problem solver with strong skills in troubleshooting and editing code. Supportive leader with positive attitude and highly energetic personality. Proficient in the Java, Python, and MEAN stacks with a desire to learn more.

EXPERIENCE

Codecademy, Online

June 2019 - Present

Skill Researching

- Earned 229+ Badges (cont.)
- Gained 964+ Points (cont.)

Codewars, Online

July 2018 - Present

Skill Researching

- Completed 135+ algorithm and code challenges (cont.)
- Leveled up to 6 kyu (JavaScript, Python, Java) with 187 honor (cont.)

uCertify, Bellingham, WA

March 2019

Review and Feedback on JavaScript Course

- Previewed and reviewed course CIW JavaScript Specialist 1D0-735
- Detailed article with feedback on LinkedIn

themorningblunt.com, Bellingham, WA

October 2018

Consultant/Developer on existing WordPress Site

- Implemented SEO with guidance for future SEO of site
- Consulted on layout and design
- Built and implemented multiple menus

Coding Dojo, Seattle, WA

April 2018 - July 2018

Student Developer

- Web Fundamentals (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery)
- Python 3 (flask with MySQL, Django with SQLite, AJAX, API)
- MEAN (JavaScript, Node, Express, Angular, MongoDB/Mongoose, Socket.io, NPM)
- Java (Spring MVC with MySQL, Tomcat, JSP, JPA)

EDUCATION

Coding Dojo
Full Stack Developer Certificate

April 2018 – July 2018

University of Washington Certificate in Editing

January 2016 - September 2016

SKILLS

- Hard Skills: Web Development, Data Structures, Debugging, Troubleshooting, Problem Solving, Object Orientated Programming
- Soft Skills: Creativity, Adaptability, Willingness to Learn, Dependable, Leadership, Critical Thinking, Analytical, Team Building, Communication, Collaboration, Inquisitiveness, Enthusiasm, Positive Attitude, Excellent Written Skills

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Fremont Brewing: Beertender
Keenan's at the Pier: Bartender
Nice Moves Moving: Lead
Hurricane Cafe: Server Manager

September 2019 – Present September 2018 – September 2019 December 2015 – April 2018 July 2003 – January 2015